{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Fill the blanks in these movie titles. ",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Oz",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Wizard of __"
  }, {
    "answer": "Apes",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Planet of the ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lambs",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Silence of the _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Music",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Sound of _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lost Ark",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Raiders of the ____ ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "Wall Street",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Wolf of ____ ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Galaxy",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Guardians of the ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Arabia",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Lawrence of ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Dead",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Shaun of the ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Hazzard",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Dukes of _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Wrath",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Grapes of _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Thieves",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Robin Hood: Prince of _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Horrors",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Little Shop of _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Summer",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "(500) Days of ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Solace",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Quantum of ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Endearment",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Terms of __________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Dreams",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Field of ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Traveling Pants",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Sisterhood of the _________ _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Penguins",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "March of the ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Mohicans",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Last of the ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Universe",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Masters of the ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Scotland",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Last King of ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Dollars",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "A Fistful of _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Christ",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Last Temptation of ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Madison County",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Bridges of _______ ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "All Fears",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Sum of ___ _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Alcatraz",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "Birdman of ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Vanities",
    "category": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
    "question": "The Bonfire of the ________"
  }],
  "quizLength": 28,
  "title": "'Of Something' Movie Titles",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/of-something-movie-titles-quiz.php"
}